A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 3, Accession 2017:059 FA1410
Rockefeller Archive Center
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 3, Accession 2017:059
1975-2015
Rockefeller Archive Center
Henry Luce Foundation
FA1410
37.84 Cubic Feet 86 letter sized document boxes
Biographical / Historical
The Henry Luce Foundation was established by Henry R. Luce in 1936. As a New York-based nonprofit organization, the Luce Foundation awards grants in American Art, Asian studies, Higher Education, Theology, and supports the Clare Boothe Luce Program for women in science, mathematics, and engineering.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the Henry Luce Foundation in 2017.
Related Materials
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 1, Accession 2017:057 (FA1317)
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 2, Accession 2017:058 (FA1393)
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 4, Accession 2017:060 (FA1442)
Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 5, Accession 2017:061 (FA1472)
Scope and Contents
The Henry Luce Foundation records (Record Group 3) contain grant files and information on projects supported by the Luce Fund for Asian Studies.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
The Henry Luce Foundation records (Record Group 3) are arranged as follows:
Series 1: Project Files, 1982-2015
Series 2: Luce Fund for Asian Studies, 1975-2013
Education (Higher); Religion; Theology; Asian studies; Art, American
- Project Files, 1982-2015; 1
  - Chron Files, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 1-6, Box 2, Folder 7-12)
  - Ackland Art Museum - Five Faiths Project, 2000-2012 (Box 3, Folder 13-15)
  - Ackland Art Museum - Five Faiths Project (Renewal), 2005-2012 (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
  - Addison Gallery of American Art - Access Addison: Electronic Access to Permanent Collection, 2006-2010 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Addison Gallery of American Art - American Vanguards: Graham, Davis, Gorky, and de Kooning, 1927-1942, 2010-2013 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Addison Gallery of American Art - William Wegman, 2004-2014 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Akron Art Museum - American Art Collection, 2005-2010 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Akron Art Museum - American Art Renewal Fund: Curator and Art Handler Positions, 2011-2013 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Albany Institute of History and Art - Asher B. Durand Painting, 2006-2011 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Albright Knox Art Gallery - Robert Mangold Retrospective, 2005-2010 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Allegheny College - French Creek Environmental Program, 2002-2012 (Box 5, Folder 25-27)
  - American Abroad Media - Public Radio Program on Religion and International Affairs, 2007-2010 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - American Alumni of Glasgow University - Survey and Feasibility Study of American Art in UK Publications, 2009-2010 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - American Association of Museums - Annual Meeting, 2006-2010 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - American Bible Society - "Biblical Art and the Asian Imagination", 2004-2012 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - American Bible Society - Biblical Arts Symposium, 2000-2012 (Box 6, Folder 32-34)
  - American College of the Building Arts - Library Collection, 2006-2011 (Box 6, Folder 35-36)
  - American Council on Education - At Home in the World: Educating for Global Connections and Local Commitments, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - American Council on Education - Fellowship Program, 2000-2009 (Box 7, Folder 38-39)
  - American Council on Education - Internationalization Forum of Chief Academic Officers, 2004-2009 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - American Council of Learned Societies - American Art Dissertation Fellowship Program (Renewal), 2007-2009 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - American Federation of Art - Color as Field: American Painting, 1950-1975, 2005-2009 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - American Folk Art Museum - Archival Research and Access, 2009-2012 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - American Jewish Committee - Jewish-Catholic Relations Seminar for Latino Seminarians, 2006-2013 (Box 8, Folder 44-45)
  - American Maritime History Project - Maritime History of the United States, 2000-2009 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - American Museum in Britain - American Folk Art Collection, 2009-2012 (Box 8, Folder 47-48)
  - American Public Media - Marketplace: China and East Asia, 2008-2011 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - American Studies Association - Asian Scholars at ASA's Annual Meeting, 2007-2009 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Americans for the Arts - National Arts Index, 2008-2010 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Amon Carter Museum - Charles Demuth: Regionalism and Modern American Art, 2003-2015 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Andover Newton Theological School - Bangor Theological Seminary and Colgate Rochester Crozer Divinity School, 2006-2009 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Appalachian Ministries Educational Resource Center (AMERC) - Consortial Theological Education in Appalachia, 2004-2013 (Box 9, Folder 54-55)
  - Archives of American Art (Smithsonian Institution) - Archives of American Art Journal, 2008-2011 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Art Institute of Chicago - Volume II of the American Art Collection Catalog, 2006-2011 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - ArtTable, Inc. - Women Arts Professionals, 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Art21, Inc. - Archive, 2005-2010 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Asbury Theological Seminary - Religious Revival Movements, 2007-2013 (Box 10, Folder 60-62)
  - Asia Foundation - American Studies Program in Vietnam, 2003-2011 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Asia Foundation - Chinese Legal Officials Training for WTO Compliance, 2001-2011 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Asia Foundation - Luce Scholars Program Anniversary Symposium, 2004-2011 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Asia Foundation - United States-China Relations Education and Exchange Program, 2008-2012 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Asia Society - Ancient Arts in Vietnam, 2004-2010 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Association for Asian Studies - Globalize and Diversify the Association for Asian Studies Annual Meeting, 2008-2011 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Association for Theological Education in Southeast Asia (ATESA), 2001-2005 (Box 11, Folder 69-70)
  - Baptist Theological Seminary at Richmond - School of Christian Ministry, 2003-2013 (Box 12, Folder 71-72)
  - Bard College - Learning Across Borders, 2006-2012 (Box 12, Folder 73-74)
  - Berkeley Art Museum and Pacific Film Archive - American Art Collection, 2003-2008 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Berkeley Art Museum and Pacific Film Archive - BAM/PFA Images (Box 12, Folder 75)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Boston University - Scripture and the Literary Arts, 2004-2012 (Box 13, Folder 76-77)
  - Boston University School of Theology - Faith-Based Conflict Transformation Pilot Program, 2004-2012 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Boston University School of Theology - Religion, Conflict, and Peace, 2008-2013 (Box 13, Folder 79-80)
  - Boston University School of Theology - Religion/Theology/Philosophy Library Planning Grant, 1993-2012 (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - Brown University - Luce Foundation Initiative on Public Policy and the Environment, 2010-2012 (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - Brown University - WISE, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - Bucknell University - Susquehanna Institute, 2007-2012 (Box 14, Folder 83-86, Box 15, Folder 87)
  - Calvin College - Faculty Seminars in Worship, 2000-2012 (Box 15, Folder 88)
  - Camden Conference - Religion as a Force in World Affairs, 2007-2009 (Box 15, Folder 89)
  - CASE Conference - Issues and Trends in Corporate and Foundation Philanthropy, John W. Cook Pet Peeves Lecture, 1995-1996 (Box 60, Folder 380)
  - Catholic Theological Union - Interfaith Dialogue and Reconciliation Internship Program, 2004-2012 (Box 15, Folder 90)
  - Catholic Theological Union - Interreligious Dialogue, 2008-2012 (Box 60, Folder 381-382)
  - Center for Plant Conservation - Recovery Potential for Imperiled Plants, 2005-2012 (Box 15, Folder 91)
  - Center for Research Libraries - Southeast Asia Microform Project: Vietnam, 1993-2009 (Box 15, Folder 92-93)
  - Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS) - Chinese Images of the United States, 2003-2011 (Box 16, Folder 94)
  - Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS) - Dismantlement of North Korea Nuclear Weapons, 2003-2005 (Box 16, Folder 95)
  - Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS) - Young Leaders Fellowship Program, 2006-2009 (Box 16, Folder 96-97)
  - Center of Theological Inquiry - Senior Scholar for Research, 2000-2012 (Box 16, Folder 98)
  - Central Baptist Theological Seminary - Myanmar Institute of Theology, 2009-2012 (Box 16, Folder 99-100)
  - Chicago Botanic Garden - Seeds of Success: Seed Banking in the Midwest Prairie, 2006-2012 (Box 17, Folder 101-102)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary - Initiative in the Arts and Theology, 2003-2011 (Box 61, Folder 383-384)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary - Spring 2005 Interim Report Attachment B: Una Celebracion/A Celebration: TEC 777 Ecclesiology in Context, Fall 2004, Deb Pyne, Gregory Potts, Jennifer Parson, Chris Warfield, David Inglis (Box 61, Folder 383-384)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary - Spring 2005 Interim Report Attachment C: Center for Community Transformation (CCT) St. Paul's (Box 61, Folder 383-384)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary - Spring 2005 Interim Report Attachment E: Making New History (Box 61, Folder 383-384)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary - Making New History, 150 Years, 1855-2005 (Box 61, Folder 383-384)
  - China Institute in America - Chinese History, Culture, and Contemporary Society, 2003-2012 (Box 17, Folder 103)
  - China Institute in America - Educational Program (Renewal), 1999-2012 (Box 17, Folder 104)
  - Cincinnati Art Museum - Bessie Potter Vonnoh: Sculptor of Women, 2005-2009 (Box 17, Folder 105)
  - Clark Art Institute - Sterling and Francine Conference on Asian Art History, 2006-2008 (Box 17, Folder 106)
  - Cleveland Museum of Art - American Art Collection, 2006-2009 (Box 18, Folder 107-108)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - American Folk Art Collection, 2005-2007 (Box 18, Folder 109-110)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - American Folk Art Collection: AARFAM Exhibits PP, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 109-110)
  - Columbia University Libraries - Internships for The New Leader Magazine, 2007-2012 (Box 18, Folder 111)
  - Committee of One Hundred - Survey of General Public, Business, and Opinion Leaders in the United States and China, 2007-2013 (Box 18, Folder 112)
  - Computing Research Association - Clare Boothe Luce Scholarships, 2003-2012 (Box 18, Folder 113)
  - Congressional Research Service (Library of Congress) - Orientation for New Members of the 11th Congress, 2008-2009 (Box 19, Folder 114)
  - Council for a Community of Democracies - Emerging Democracies Education Programs, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 115)
  - Council for a Parliament of the World's Religions - Parliament and Assembly, 2004-2007 (Box 61, Folder 385)
  - Defenders of Wildlife - Wildlife Trade, Invasive Species, and Human Health, 2006-2012 (Box 19, Folder 116)
  - Delaware Art Museum - Seeing the City: Soan's New York, 2004-2009 (Box 19, Folder 117)
  - Denver Art Museum - Contemporary Rhythm: Art of Ernest L. Blumenschein, 2006-2009 (Box 19, Folder 118-118A)
    Closed to research - contains personnel and financial materials.
  - Dia Center for the Arts - Alfred Jensen, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 119)
  - Dickinson College - Integrated Watershed-Based Field Seminars, 2004-2012 (Box 20, Folder 120-121)
  - Duke University - Economic and Art History Departments Collaboration, 1998-2010 (Box 20, Folder 122-123)
  - Duke University Divinity School - Center for Theological Writing, 2001-2012 (Box 20, Folder 124)
  - Duke University Divinity School - Post-Doctoral Fellowship in Preaching, 1996-2003 (Box 21, Folder 125)
  - East-West Center- South Korea-United States Journalist Exchange, 2005-2008 (Box 21, Folder 126)
  - East-West Center - Southeast Asia Fellowship Program, Washington, D.C., 2003-2009 (Box 21, Folder 127)
  - Eastern Cluster of Lutheran Seminaries - Seminary Libraries, 1999-2013 (Box 21, Folder 128)
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Becoming Americans: Chinese Experience, 2001-2012 (Box 21, Folder 129)
  - Environmental Broadcasting Corporation - Mississippi Delta Restoration, 2005-2012 (Box 21, Folder 130)
  - Fisher Gallery, University of Southern California - Peter Plagens, 2003-2005 (Box 22, Folder 131)
  - Forum for the Future of Higher Education - Leadership in American Higher Education, 1999-2003 (Box 22, Folder 132)
  - Foundation for a Conference on Faith and Order in North America, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 133)
  - Foundation for a Conference on Faith and Order in North America - Operating Expenses, 2003-2004 (Box 61, Folder 386-387)
  - Franklin Pierce College - Francis Cheney Lectureship in Religion and Society, 1999-2012 (Box 22, Folder 134)
  - Frick Collection - Whistler, Women and Fashion, 2002-2004 (Box 22, Folder 135)
  - Fuller Theological Seminary - Brehm Center for Worship, Theology, and the Arts, 2003-2013 (Box 62, Folder 388-390)
  - Fuller Theological Seminary - Traditions of Religious Leadership, 1999-2013 (Box 22, Folder 136)
  - Fuller Theological Seminary - Worship and Art in Global and Multicultural Context, 2007-2012 (Box 62, Folder 391-393)
  - Fuller Theological Seminary - Sacred Imagery Slideshow: Brehm Center for Worship, Theology and the Arts, 2007 (Box 62, Folder 391-393)
  - Fuller Theological Seminary - Global Preaching Initiative (Box 62, Folder 391-393)
  - Fuller Theological Seminary - Songs of Divine Love: An Islamic/Christian Spiritual Concert by the Classical Arabic Music Ensemble, 2009 (Box 62, Folder 391-393)
  - Fuller Theological Seminary - Tarab wa Watar, 2009 (Box 62, Folder 391-393)
  - Garrett Evangelical Theological Seminary - Educational Planning and Evaluation, 2003-2013 (Box 63, Folder 394-395)
  - George Washington University and Woodrow Wilson Center - East Asia Policy Program, American Scholars, 2000-2009 (Box 63, Folder 396)
  - Gibbes Museum of Art - Washington Allston, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 138)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Center for Urban Ministerial Education, 2002-2012 (Box 23, Folder 139-141)
  - Graduate Theological Union - Asian Theologies and Perspectives in North American Education, 2003-2013 (Box 63, Folder 397-399)
  - Graduate Theological Union - Religion and Visual Arts Program, 1996-2013 (Box 64, Folder 400-401)
  - Green-Wood Cemetery - Saved in Time (Henry Luce Foundation Staff) (Box 23, Folder 142)
  - Group Against Smog and Pollution (GASP) - Diesel Emissions, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 137)
  - Samuel P. Harn Museum of Art (University of Florida) - American Art Collection, 2006-2009 (Box 23, Folder 143)
  - Hartley Film Foundation - Controversies on Sexuality within Episcopal Church, 2007-2012 (Box 64, Folder 402)
  - Harvard University, Divinity School - Urban Ministry and Renewal of Civil Society, 1995-2007 (Box 23, Folder 144-145)
  - Harvard University, Kennedy School - Justice in Times of Transition, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 146)
  - Healthcare Chaplaincy - Clinical Pastoral Education Program, 2007-2012 (Box 24, Folder 147-149)
  - Hebrew Union College, 2001-2012 (Box 24, Folder 150-151)
  - Hispanic Summer Program - Faculty Development, 2000-2012 (Box 25, Folder 152)
  - Hospitality Committee for United Nations Delegation - Orientation, 2003-2004 (Box 64, Folder 403)
  - Iliff Theological School - Rural Ministries Program, 1995-2001 (Box 25, Folder 153)
  - In Trust, Inc. - The Magazine for Leaders in Theological Education, 2004-2006 (Box 25, Folder 154-155)
  - In Trust, Inc. - Recruit and Train New Writers, 2007-2013 (Box 64, Folder 404-405, Box 65, Folder 406-407)
  - Interfaith Youth Core - Interfaith Action in the World and Religious Understanding, 2005-2013 (Box 65, Folder 408-410)
  - Interfaith Youth Core - Chicago Season of Interfaith Youth Service, Chicago Tonight, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 408-410)
  - Interfaith Youth Core - Leadership for a Religiously Diverse World, 2009-2013 (Box 65, Folder 411-412)
  - Institute for International Economics - East Asian Regionalism and the World Economy, 2004-2012 (Box 25, Folder 156)
  - Institute of International Education - Elisabeth Luce Moore Leadership Program for Chinese Women, 2003-2009 (Box 25, Folder 157)
  - Institute of Museum and Library Services - Connecting to Collections Bookshelf, 2008-2009 (Box 26, Folder 158)
  - Institute of Museum and Library Services - Conservation Bookshelf, 2007-2009 (Box 26, Folder 159-160)
  - Institute of Museum and Library Services - National Conservation Summit, 2007-2009 (Box 66, Folder 413)
  - Institute for Social Policy and Understanding - Retreat and Roundtables, Washington, D.C., 2011-2012 (Box 26, Folder 161)
  - International Board of Education of the Church of the Nazarene - Asian Theologians in a Consultation on Global Theological Education, 2006-2013 (Box 66, Folder 414)
  - International Crisis Group - Indonesia Project, 2002-2005 (Box 26, Folder 162-163)
  - International Institute for Mediation and Historical Conciliation - Delhi Colloquium, 2005-2007 (Box 66, Folder 415)
  - International Law Students Association - Jessup Competition, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 416)
  - International Partnership for Service Learning - Church Related College in Asia, 2000-2004 (Box 27, Folder 164-165)
  - International Student Conferences - Korean-American Student Conferences, 2007-2009 (Box 27, Folder 166)
  - Iowa State University Museums - Albert Paley: Portals and Gates, 2006-2008 (Box 27, Folder 167)
  - Japan Society - Early Buddhist Art from Korea, 2002-2005 (Box 27, Folder 168)
  - Japan Society - United States-Japan Innovators Project, 2007-2013 (Box 28, Folder 169-170)
  - Jesuit School of Theology, Berkeley - Christology in Pacific Rim Cultures, 2006-2012 (Box 28, Folder 171)
  - Jesuit School of Theology, Berkeley - Pacific Rim Initiative, 2000-2006 (Box 28, Folder 172)
  - Jesuit School of Theology, Berkeley - Theological Aesthetics, 2007-2013 (Box 28, Folder 173)
  - Jesuit School of Theology, Berkeley - Beauty: The Color of Truth, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 173)
  - The Jewish Museum - Louise Nevelson: A Story in Sculpture, 2006-2008 (Box 29, Folder 174)
  - Jewish Theological Seminary - Summer Institute of Jewish Art, 2003-2011 (Box 29, Folder 175-177)
  - John Jay College of Criminal Justice - Child Sexual Abuse in the Catholic Church, 2007-2011 (Box 29, Folder 178-179)
  - Johns Hopkins University - China's Xinjiang Uighur Autonomous Region, 2000-2013 (Box 30, Folder 180-181)
  - Johns Hopkins University - International Environmental Practicum, 2007-2012 (Box 30, Folder 182)
  - Journal of Feminist Studies in Religion - Teaching for Change, 2004-2012 (Box 30, Folder 183)
  - Judson Memorial Church - Public Ministry Training Center, 2007-2013 (Box 30, Folder 184)
  - Lawyers Committee for Human Rights - Human Rights in China through Legal Reform, 1998-2013 (Box 30, Folder 185)
  - Library of Congress - New Member Seminar for 108th Congress, 2002-2003 (Box 31, Folder 186)
  - Louisville Theological Seminary - Academic Support Services, 2000-2004 (Box 31, Folder 187-188)
  - Luce Center, Atlanta, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 189)
  - Lutheran Theological Seminary at Philadelphia - Asian Theological Initiative, Multicultural Mission Resource Center, 2006-2009 (Box 31, Folder 190)
  - Lyman Allyn Art Museum - At Home and Abroad: Christopher Pearse Cranch, 2004-2009 (Box 31, Folder 191)
  - Maryland Historical Society - American Collection Research and Access (ACE), 1997-2005 (Box 32, Folder 192)
  - Maryland Historical Society - American Genius: B. Henry Latrobe, 2006-2010 (Box 32, Folder 193)
  - Marymount Manhattan College - Writing Center, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 194)
  - Master of Professional Studies Program, Sing Sing: A UPN-9 Documentary (Box 32, Folder 194)
  - McDowell Mountain Ranch Soccer Club and North Scottsdale Soccer Club - Margaret Werner, 2008-2012 (Box 32, Folder 195)
  - Memorial Art Gallery (University of Rochester) - American Collection Enhancement (ACE) Initiative, 1999-2006 (Box 32, Folder 196)
  - Memphis Theological Seminary - Institute on Theology and the Arts, 2009-2012 (Box 32, Folder 197-199)
  - Memphis Theological Seminary - Return Beat (Box 32, Folder 197-199)
  - Mepkin Abbey - Clare Boothe Luce Library, 2000-2006 (Box 33, Folder 200-201)
  - Mepkin Abbey - Father Francis Memorial Building Fund, 2006-2013 (Box 33, Folder 202)
  - Methodist Theological School of Ohio - Center for Christian Leadership, 2002-2006 (Box 33, Folder 203)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Henry R. Luce Center for the Study of American Art, 2004-2008 (Box 33, Folder 204-205)
  - Middlebury College - Issue and Impact: Coexistence and the Global Environment, 2004-2009 (Box 34, Folder 206)
  - Missouri Botanical Garden - Transboundary Initiatives for Botanical Conservation and Education to Improve Protected Area Systems Management in Indochina (TRICEPS), 2005-2009 (Box 34, Folder 207-208)
  - Monastic Interreligious Dialogue, 2003-2005 (Box 34, Folder 209)
  - Morehouse College - Howard Thurman Papers, 1997-2012 (Box 34, Folder 210)
  - Museum of Art (Rhode Island School of Design) - Interior Drama: Aaron Siskind's Photographs of the 1940s, 2003-2004 (Box 34, Folder 211)
  - Museum of the City of New York - Alchemy of Ink: Al Hirschfeld's New York, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 212)
  - Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles - Robert Smithson Retrospective, 2003-2005 (Box 35, Folder 213-214)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston - Latino Art Documents, 2007-2009 (Box 35, Folder 215-216)
  - Museum of Modern Art - Archive Collections, 2005-2009 (Box 35, Folder 217)
  - Naropa University - Peter Goldfarb Institute for Advances Theatre Studies, 2002-2005 (Box 35, Folder 218)
  - National Building Museum - Richard Neutra's "Windshield", 2002-2003 (Box 35, Folder 219)
  - National Center for Leadership, 2003-2010 (Box 35, Folder 220)
  - National Gallery of Art - American Art Publications Fund, 2006-2008 (Box 36, Folder 221)
  - National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian - Inventing Marcel Duchamp: The Dynamics of Portraiture, 2008-2009 (Box 36, Folder 222)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council - Green Buildings Education Initiative, 2001-2004 (Box 36, Folder 223)
  - Nautilus of America, Inc. - Northeast Asia Peace and Security Network, 2005-2011 (Box 36, Folder 224-225)
  - Nazarene Theological Seminary - Collaborative Programming with Asia, Africa, and South America Seminaries, 2008-2013 (Box 37, Folder 226-227)
  - Nelson-Atkins Museum of Art - American Art Collection, 2006-2009 (Box 37, Folder 228-229)
  - The Network, Inc and Human Media - "Barely Getting By" (Public Radio Documentary Series), 2007-2009 (Box 37, Folder 230)
  - The Network, Inc and Human Media - "Barely Getting By" Stories of American's Working Poor, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 230)
    Scope and Contents
    Written and produced by David Freudberg. Distributed by NPR and PRI.
  - The Network, Inc. and Human Media - "Barely Getting By" Humankind #126/127 Answering the Needs (Parts 1 and 2), 2008 (Box 37, Folder 230)